[
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find a 'Brummie'?",
    "correctAnswer": "west-midlands"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find the Angel of the North?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-east"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region were the Beatles formed?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find Windsor Castle?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-east"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region is home to Glastonbury Festival?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region is the capital of the UK?",
    "correctAnswer": "london"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region is Coronation Street filmed?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'The Humber Bridge'?",
    "correctAnswer": "yorkshire-and-the-humber"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'The University of Cambridge'?",
    "correctAnswer": "eastern"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find the 'Stonehenge'?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Anfield' football stadium?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find the 'White Cliffs of Dover?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-east"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Blackpool tower'?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find the 'Roman baths'?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Ben Nevis'?",
    "correctAnswer": "scotland"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find the 'Jurassic coast'?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find the 'Eden Project?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Snowdon'?",
    "correctAnswer": "wales"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'The University of Oxford'?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-east"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Old Trafford' football stadium?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Lake Windermere'?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Sherwood Forest'?",
    "correctAnswer": "east-midlands"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Stamford Bridge' football stadium?",
    "correctAnswer": "london"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does the 'Bury black pudding' originate from?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does 'Laverbread' originate from?",
    "correctAnswer": "wales"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do 'Cockles' originate from?",
    "correctAnswer": "london"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does 'Scouse' originate from?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do 'Cornish pasties' originate from?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Alton Towers'?",
    "correctAnswer": "west-midlands"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Chester Zoo'?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-west"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Thorpe Park'?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-east"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region is 'Towie' filmed?",
    "correctAnswer": "eastern"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region was golf first invented?",
    "correctAnswer": "scotland"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region is home to 'Rugby'?",
    "correctAnswer": "west-midlands"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Durham Cathedral'?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-east"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Hadrianâ€™s Wall'?",
    "correctAnswer": "north-east"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Tower Bridge'?",
    "correctAnswer": "london"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Brighton Palace Pier'?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-east"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'The Iron Bridge'?",
    "correctAnswer": "west-midlands"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Chatsworth House'?",
    "correctAnswer": "east-midlands"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Canterbury Cathedral'?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-east"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region would you find 'Canterbury Cathedral'?",
    "correctAnswer": "south-east"
  }

]
